<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Visions of the future on IB English - Antonio Kam</title>
    <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/tags/visions-of-the-future/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Visions of the future on IB English - Antonio Kam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 14:07:10 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/tags/visions-of-the-future/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini IO</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/visions-of-the-future/mini-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 14:07:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/visions-of-the-future/mini-io/</guid>
      <description>Recently I did the Mini IO as part of a school summative assessment (notes for which can be found here), and scored pretty poorly on it. However, here are some general notes that I can follow in order to improve my performance for next time:
 Explicitly state your global issue right from the beginning  Identify how it&#39;s presented in the text in the introduction (ie this issue is widespread globally because x)   Clearly signpost your work (this needs particular work)  I will divide this into 3 main arguments, x, y and z.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photojournalism - Quick Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/visions-of-the-future/photographs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 08:59:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/visions-of-the-future/photographs/</guid>
      <description>Question We study photojournalism in LangLit because the IBO defines photographs as a type of ‘text’. Based on what we have explored today, why do you think this might be the case?
 There&#39;s a pretty famous quote - &amp;ldquo;A photo is worth a thousand words&amp;rdquo;, and thus, photojournalism can state a lot even without many words. Especially with the quality of current photography, as well as the multitude of global issues around the world, photographs in the modern world are as important as they have ever been, being able to move people emotionally (for example with a war photograph single-handedly being able to sway public opinion on the Vietnam war.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>