<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IB English - Antonio Kam</title>
    <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/</link>
    <description>Recent content on IB English - Antonio Kam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 18:35:35 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Weather</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/paper1/cold-weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 18:35:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/paper1/cold-weather/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free the Slaves</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/paper1/free-the-slaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 18:34:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/paper1/free-the-slaves/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poverty</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/paper1/poverty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 18:31:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/paper1/poverty/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Phoenix Gone</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/chin/the-phoenix-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 18:30:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/chin/the-phoenix-gone/</guid>
      <description>Analysis  Reflection I did not enjoy this poem at all. It was way too long for my tastes, and I felt like there wasn&#39;t too much content that struck me (essentially, a lot of filler content). However, the end of the poem was a hard hitting one for me.
 &amp;ldquo;yellow crowfoot in the pond, not lotus, not lily&amp;rdquo;
 This was hard hitting for me as it made me remember to be grateful for what I have, and to not take anything for granted again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Repulse Bay</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/chin/repulse-bay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 18:30:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/chin/repulse-bay/</guid>
      <description>Analysis  Reflection Repulse Bay was quite a hard-hitting poem for me. Chin doesn&#39;t feel quite at home with her culture, and is stuck between two boundaries - Western culture and Chinese culture. I myself am also part of this cultural shift, with the modern Hong Kong being less integrated with Chinese culture, and more integrated with international culture. I think one aspect of it can be seen with public holidays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Got That Name</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/chin/how-i-got-that-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 18:41:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/chin/how-i-got-that-name/</guid>
      <description>Analysis  Summary How I Got That Name by Marilyn Chin is a poem where she explores the issue of her culture being part of both the east and the west. She explores the issue of her name - there is both an English component and a Chinese component. She explores how she believes that even if she tries to avoid her Chinese roots in the USA, it will only come back to her at an even stronger intensity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Final IO</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/assessments/io/final-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 14:28:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/assessments/io/final-io/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I&#39;ll essentially be reflecting on how I got to my global issue, and the general problems/solutions I had while doing my IO.
 Getting to my global issue I was very interested in the Nike advertisements studied earlier in the year due to the message hitting home for me (I had to endure some hardships in terms of not being able to chase some of my dreams), so I felt like for my global issue, I wanted to explore how authors explored these issues with the way they portrayed the text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resilience</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/commonlit/resilience/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 19:58:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/commonlit/resilience/</guid>
      <description>This was my first assignment done on CommonLit.
Here are a few notes that I have taken on the article:
 PAF  P: This article was made primarily to inform readers about what successful people + businesses do in order to stay afloat in rough times, and how certain traits can lead to success. A: As this article was part of the Harvard Business Review, this would lead to a more business-focused article - ie more of the text would be based around the idea of how businesses apply resilience and what they look for in candidates F: A long first person article about many examples (and 3 different traits) of resilience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini IO</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/visions-of-the-future/mini-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 14:07:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/visions-of-the-future/mini-io/</guid>
      <description>Recently I did the Mini IO as part of a school summative assessment (notes for which can be found here), and scored pretty poorly on it. However, here are some general notes that I can follow in order to improve my performance for next time:
 Explicitly state your global issue right from the beginning  Identify how it&#39;s presented in the text in the introduction (ie this issue is widespread globally because x)   Clearly signpost your work (this needs particular work)  I will divide this into 3 main arguments, x, y and z.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photojournalism - Quick Thoughts</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/visions-of-the-future/photographs-&#43;-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 08:59:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/visions-of-the-future/photographs-&#43;-videos/</guid>
      <description>Question We study photojournalism in LangLit because the IBO defines photographs as a type of ‘text’. Based on what we have explored today, why do you think this might be the case?
 There&#39;s a pretty famous quote - &amp;ldquo;A photo is worth a thousand words&amp;rdquo;, and thus, photojournalism can state a lot even without many words. Especially with the quality of current photography, as well as the multitude of global issues around the world, photographs in the modern world are as important as they have ever been, being able to move people emotionally (for example with a war photograph single-handedly being able to sway public opinion on the Vietnam war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nature vs Nurture</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/frankenstein/nature-vs-nurture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 09:32:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/frankenstein/nature-vs-nurture/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mini IO Planning</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/frankenstein/io-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 09:29:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/frankenstein/io-planning/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frankenstein Notes</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/frankenstein/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 09:27:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/frankenstein/notes/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Brief Planning</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/advertisements/nike/creative-brief-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 12:50:26 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/advertisements/nike/creative-brief-planning/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Brief</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/advertisements/nike/creative-brief/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 12:33:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/advertisements/nike/creative-brief/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summative - Unicef Tap Project</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/advertisements/summative/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 14:54:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/advertisements/summative/</guid>
      <description>Essay In this advertisement by Unicef promoting their ‘Tap Project’ aimed at adults and families, the issue of access to clean water is highlighted. The advertisement aims to inform readers about the project, and also gives readers a chance to reflect on how fortunate they are to live with effortless access to water.
To begin with, this advertisement was created in early 2016, a time when the world was generally educated about global issues, and understood that some places were not fortunate enough to have access to basic needs such as clean water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Notes - Advertising</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/advertisements/basic-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 21:38:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/advertisements/basic-notes/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Issues Essay</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/persepolis/global-issues-essay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 12:27:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/posts/persepolis/global-issues-essay/</guid>
      <description>The Passport (page 118) Global Issue: The impacts of political oppression on families.
 In ‘Persepolis’ by Marjane Satrapi, the ubiquitous global issue of political oppression is a recurring motif. In the chapter ‘The Passport’, Satrapi uses linguistic and graphical features in subtle manners as vehicles to illustrate her ideas on the political environment in Iran, as well as the lack of freedom that people get in such environments.
To begin with, on the bottom right panel on page 122 (Satrapi, 2009), Satrapi shows the negative side of a politically oppressed environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rouxles.github.io/anto-ib-english/about/</guid>
      <description>IB English This is my learner portfolio for IB English Language and Literature.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>